http://www.phillytour.com/privacy-policy-web-app-terms-use/

0
215-389-TOUR (8687)
tours availableClick flag for translation
76 Carriage Company Inc. DBA Philadelphia Trolley Works and 76 Carriage Tours LLP takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about how 76 Carriage Company Inc. DBA Philadelphia Trolley Works and 76 Carriage Tours LLP collects, stores, uses, and shares, information provided by you when you use our products and services.
What This Privacy Policy Covers
This policy covers how 76 Carriage Company Inc. DBA Philadelphia Trolley Works and 76 Carriage Tours LLP collects, stores, uses, and shares the information that 76 Carriage Company Inc. DBA Philadelphia Trolley Works and 76 Carriage Tours LLP collects and receives from you, including information related to your past use of 76 Carriage Company Inc. DBA Philadelphia Trolley Works and 76 Carriage Tours LLP products and services.
Information Collection and Use
76 Carriage Company Inc. DBA Philadelphia Trolley Works and 76 Carriage Tours LLP  collects information from you when you use the 76 Carriage Company Inc. DBA Philadelphia Trolley Works and 76 Carriage Tours LLP, sign up for our e-newsletter, purchase products, request information from us or use our real time Web App.
When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, zip code, occupation, and industry. When you use the Web App, we also collect location information from you so that we can provide you with the Web App’s services. The Web App uses the Google Maps APIs to show you where our trolleys and buses are located in relation to you. Therefore, in addition to this Privacy Policy, your use of the Web App is subject to Google’s Privacy Policy available at https://www.google.com/policies/privacy. By using the Web App, you also agree to be bound by Google’s Terms of Service available at https://developers.google.com/maps/documentation/.
76 Carriage Company Inc. DBA Philadelphia Trolley Works and 76 Carriage Tours LLP uses information for the following general purposes: provide you our products and, send bi-monthly emails, and contact you.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
76 Carriage Company Inc. DBA Philadelphia Trolley Works and 76 Carriage Tours LLP does not rent or sell your information to other people or nonaffiliated companies. 76 Carriage Company Inc. DBA Philadelphia Trolley Works and 76 Carriage Tours LLP shares information with third party service providers that help us provide our products and services to you (including, but not limited to, Google). We may share with, rent to, or sell to third parties information that does not identify a user who may also further sell, rent, or share such information to or with other people or companies that may also provide products and services to you. For example, we, or our service providers may sell aggregated location information, which does not identify an individual user, to local food vendors, so that those vendors know when to expect lunchtime traffic at one of our stops, or to owners of public restrooms, so that they may know when to expect high traffic at a particular public restroom.
Confidentiality and Security
We limit access to information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs or to third parties we engage to help us provide our products and services to you.
We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
76 Carriage Company Inc. DBA Philadelphia Trolley Works and 76 Carriage Tours LLP may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your 76 Carriage Company Inc. DBA Philadelphia Trolley Works and 76 Carriage Tours LLP account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
Return Policy:
All internet sales are final. In the event that service is considered unsatisfactory, refunds will be considered on redeemed vouchers by sending a letter and a copy of tour tickets to:
76 Carriage Company Inc.
Please direct any questions and suggestions to us at:
76 Carriage Company Inc.
Please Call: 215-389-TOUR (8687)
Fax: 215-389-1279
Email: info@phillytour.com for general info
Email: charters@phillytour.com for charter or special information
For Horse Drawn Carriage
Please Call: 215-923-8516
Fax: 215-923-7776
Email: 76Carriage@phillytour.com
© 2018 Philadelphia Trolley Works and Carriage Company. All Rights Reserved.     Privacy Policy
215.389.TOUR (8687)
Search
